One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
in the blank slates of our minds
Sanji vs. Jabra
Sanji-kun!
Sanji...!
How did you get out of that state?!
A bathtub fell from the sky and broke the spell.
I suppose it's because I got wet.
More importantly, Nami-san...
Did you fall in love with me again?!
I wish the bathtub had hit you directly.
Nosopp!
So now it's at the point where you're not
using any part of Sogeking in my name.
I-I'm sorry, Sanji-kun.
I...
After all... I...
All that matters is you're still alive.
Everyone has things that they
can do and things that they can't.
Sanji!
Look outside, both of you.
No way!
The Gates of Justice are about to open.
Robin!
Once those gates are opened
and Robin-chan passes through,
the sea beyond hosts a nest of sea kings,
which we can't cross.
Past that, there's the great prison
and Navy Headquarters.
Soon, Robin-chan will be taken
to a place beyond our reach.
Oh, no. Luffy didn't make it in time?
Dammit! I can't get through here!
Robin's waiting for me!
Give it up. You'll never see her again.
You can't go beyond these doors.
Rubber Rubber...
Gatling!
That technique doesn't work on me.
Now, come!
I said come! We're going to the bridge!
Am I gonna make it in time?
I hope either the No. 3 or No. 4 key frees Nico Robin!
Anyway, I have to stop them at any cost!
It's this way!
Is it this way?
Chimney! Hurry up!
It's this way!
This tower will get hit by cannon fire, too.
Wait, Grandma! I've gotta mark the way so they don't get lost!
Picking me as your opponent seems to have sealed your fate.
Hey! Let us get on board!
That's not possible! The sea train is full!
Get some ships from an outlying island!
You bastard! I thought you were strangely calm!
So you pretended to be
tied up using your own rope?!
Yeah. I was waiting for a chance.
What about Big Bro Franky?
What about the Straw Hats?
Those people are unstoppable!
They don't need us to worry about them!
We're gonna hurry up
and escape from this island!
Yeah!
Navy
Ten battleships have set sail for
the Judicial Island, Enies Lobby!
The situation couldn't be worse.
But even the worst situation always hides a fair chance.
Sanji!
Leave his key to me.
Are you changing fighters? That's fine by me.
I'll do what you can't do.
And you do what I can't do!
What?
Think carefully.
Read the situation!
As long as we have you, we can
save Robin-chan for sure! Usopp!
As long as I'm here... we can save Robin?
Shave!
Go!
O-Okay! Usopp!
Ow, ow! That hurts!
Hang in there! It's better than dying here, right?!
Good point.
Iron Body Kenpo!
Wolf Shot!
Some hunter you are. You just talk big.
Oh, that's right. I get it!
What is it?
We can save her! As long as I'm here, we can save Robin! Dammit!
"Dammit"?! You don't have
to get upset or anything!
Let's hurry, Nami-kun!
Hey, wait up!
I got it! I got it!
Hey, be quiet. That wolf's gonna come after us!
Maybe I should kill them after all.
Now you've gone and done it.
Ten Finger Pistol!
Troisième... Haché!
Third-Grade Ground Meat
Iron Body!
That doesn't work on me, you idiot!
What's with his kicks?
That technique you guys use
to make your body like iron...
is really a pain in the ass.
Tempest Kick: Lone Wolf!
Basse Côte!
Chuck Roast
Longe!
Loin
Tendron!
Skirt steak
Flanchet! Quasi! Queue! Cuisseau! Jarret!
Flank, Rump, Tail, Thigh, Shin
Veau... Shot!
Veal Shot
Iron Body Kenpo!
I said your kicks don't work on me, didn't I?!
Wolf Fang!
You felt that, didn't ya?!
That was Iron Body Kenpo: Wolf Fang Stance!
I'm the only one of the Six Powers masters...
who can move around with
Iron Body active from head to toe.
Stop your rambling!
Deuxième Haché!
Second-Grade Ground Meat
It appears to have worked,
but it actually didn't?
Well, did it or didn't it?!
Well done.
I've been waiting for a man like you.
Hm?
Would you save her... Save Robin?
What?! What're you saying?
I kept quiet about this, but... Robin is...
actually my little sister... whom I lost track of a long time ago.
What?!
Is that true?!
I didn't know.
She never told us anything about that.
I'm not surprised,
but it's true.
Please, save her!
Okay, I got it. Just leave it to me.
I'll take this key and save her without a doubt.
You think I'd buy that crap?!
Robin-chan is your little sister?
You dumbass! If you're gonna lie,
try to make it more believable.
You should have realized by now.
No matter what tricks you play,
you can never go through these doors.
You're wrong! I'll do whatever
it takes to go through there!
It seems that we disagree.
I guess there's no point in discussing it.
I don't have much time, either.
Rubber Rubber... Gatling!
Stamp!
Whip!
Spear!
Did ya feel it a little this time, wolf-kun?
Whoa! You bastard! The key!
You gave it to me!
How dare you?!
Iron Body!
– See ya!
– Ahh! Hold it!
I'm the one who has the trademark on foul play!
How dare you mock me?!
Shave!
Party Table:
Iron Body Kenpo!
Cuisseau Shoot!
Thigh Shoot
Brochette!
Skewer
Dammit! I'm pissed!
It looks like you really wanna get hurt.
Iron Body Kenpo: Wolf Plantain Stance!
Wolf Hunting LAN!
Whoa! A slashing attack?!
Heavy Treading Wolf!
What do you think of the
power of an Iron Body punch?
It's in a different league, huh?
Moon Walk!
Tempest Kick: Lupus Fall!
You were naive to think that you
could steal the key from me and run.
I'm a wolf. I'll keep after you until I make a meal of you.
Oh? You're still alive.
I don't intend to run.
I don't intend to be killed.
And I don't intend to forgive.
Forgive?
Are you sympathizing with Nico Robin?
A distracted mind just creates
openings during a fight.
If you have time to pity that ill-fated woman,
you should think of a way
to save your neck here.
Watch your mouth.
I'm the kind who heats up with anger.
If you're under strain, there's no
chance you can bring me down.
I'm sure my attacks have done
quite a bit of damage to you by now.
If that wasn't enough, then...
Iron Body Kenpo: Infernal Celestial Wolf!
Go ahead and laugh while you can.
Hm?
I don't know what's so fun
about spinning like that, but...
Hm? What's with him?
One of his feet is now red!
Devil's foot...
Diable Jambe!
The heat generated from spinning
will make my kicks even faster!
It's glowing!
Ow, it burns!
Its devastating power equals that of a devil.
It burns! Ow, ow, ow!
I-I'm burnt! Even my bones
feel hot! They're broken!
Iron Body isn't working at all!
What's with that kick?! Dammit!
How stupid!
I can't believe he'd jump into the air
when facing a Six Powers master!
Diable Jambe:
Première Haché!
First-Grade Ground Meat
Moon Walk!
How stupid!
You're really stupid!
You got carried away and hastily tried to finish the fight!
I win!
Take this!
Moonlight Ten Finger Pistol!
One of my hands got repelled.
You were close, huh?
If you were fast enough
to get another kick in,
you could've completely
stopped the Finger Pistol.
Well, I couldn't help it...
because the other kick is...
for finishing you off!
Diable Jambe!
What? W-Wait!
Flambage...
Flambé
Shot!
God creates food...
and the Devil creates spice.
I guess I made it a little too spicy.